You never forget your first love.
The Best of Me is a drama, romance film directed by Michael Hoffman.
A pair of former high school sweethearts reunite after many years
when they return to visit their small hometown.
Amanda Collier, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Dawson Cole, played by James Marsden.
Younger Dawson Cole, played by Luke Bracey.
Young Amanda Collier, played by Liana Liberato.
Tuck Hostetler, played by Gerald McRaney.
Evelyn, played by Caroline Goodall.
The Best of Me is a 2014 American romantic drama film directed by
Michael Hoffman and written by Will Fetters and J.
Mills Goodloe, based on Nicholas Sparks' 2011 novel of the same name.
The film stars James Marsden and Michelle Monaghan
with Luke Bracey and Liana Liberato.
The tone is emotional.